var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following force is the strongest force in nature?",
    answer: "Nuclear force",
    options: [
      "Electromagnetic force",
      "Nuclear force",
      "Weak force",
      "Gravitational force",
    ],
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the Father of Experimental Physics?",
    answer: "Galileo",
    options: ["Galileo", "Newton", "Albert Einstein", "Neils Bohar"],
  },

  {
    question:
      "The number of base units for measuring physical quantities according to the SI system are ____",
    answer: "7",
    options: ["1", "10", "7", "5"],
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following force is the strongest force in nature?",
    answer: "Nuclear force",
    options: [
      "Electromagnetic force",
      "Nuclear force",
      "Weak force",
      "Gravitational force",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Convert 5 N to Dynes",
    answer: "500000 Dynes",
    options: ["500000 Dynes", "500 Dynes", "5000 Dynes", "0.5 Dynes"],
  },

  {
    question: "What does a Voltmeter measure?",
    answer: "Voltage",
    options: ["Voltage", "Current", "Length", "Speed"],
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following is a unit of temperature?",
    answer: "Fahrenheit",
    options: ["Kelvin", "Degree Celsius", "Fahrenheit", "Degree"],
  },

  {
    question: "Which one of the following is a dimensionless quantity?",
    answer: "Reynolds number",
    options: ["Weight", "Specific Weight", "Mass", "Reynolds number"],
  },

  {
    question:
      "In which of the following states does a body possess kinetic energy?",
    answer: "Motion",
    options: ["Rest", "Motion", "In zero Gravity", "When placed on a platform"],
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which of the following types of motion can be used for describing the motion of a car on a straight road?",
    answer: "Rectilinear",
    options: ["Circular", "Rectilinear", "Periodic", "Harmonic Motion"],
  },

  {
    question: "What kind of motion is rectilinear motion?",
    answer: "One dimensional",
    options: [
      "Two dimensional",
      "One dimensional",
      "Three dimensional",
      "Zero dimensional",
    ],
  },

  {
    question:
      "When a body is in the state of complete rest, what kind of energy does it possess?",
    answer: "Potential Energy",
    options: [
      "Total Energy",
      "Kinetic Energy",
      "Potential Energy",
      "Boost is the power of my Energy",
    ],
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are obtained by dividing total displacement by total time taken?",
    answer: "Average velocity",
    options: [
      "Speed",
      "Average velocity",
      "Instantaneous velocity",
      "Uniform velocity",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the rate of change of rate of change of displacement of a body?",
    answer: "Average velocity",
    options: [
      "Speed",
      "Average velocity",
      "Instantaneous velocity",
      "Uniform velocity",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are obtained by dividing total displacement by total time taken?",
    answer: "Acceleration",
    options: ["Speed", "Acceleration", "Force", "Jerk"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of the following relations is true?",
    answer: "Distance >= Displacement",
    options: [
      "Distance > Displacement",
      "Distance >= Displacement",
      "Distance <= Displacement",
      "Distance < Displacement",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "A person is standing at -2 location on the number line. He runs to and fro from -2 to +5 location 5 times. How much distance has he covered if he comes back to -2 location at the end?",
    answer: "35 units",
    options: ["15 units", "25 units", "35 units", "45 units"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the path length of the following path? A (0, 0) to B (5, 0) to C (5, 5) to D (0, 5)",
    answer: "15 units",
    options: ["5 units", "10 units", "15 units", "20 units"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "When person moves in the coordinate system from A (0, 0) to B (5, 10), to C (8, 6), what is the displacement covered?",
    answer: "10 units",
    options: ["5 units", "10 units", "15 units", "7 units"],
  },

  {
    question:
      "When person moves in the coordinate system from A (0, 0) to B (5, 10), to C (8, 6), what is the displacement covered?",
    answer: "10 units",
    options: ["5 units", "10 units", "15 units", "7 units"],
  },
];
